[
  {
      "question": "ويليام",
      "response": "و ي ل ي ا م"
  },
  {
      "question": "نامي",
      "response": "ن ا م ي"
  },
  {
      "question": "لوفي",
      "response": "ل و ف ي"
  },
  {
      "question": "ايرين",
      "response": "ا ي ر ي ن"
  },
  {
      "question": "استا",
      "response": "ا س ت ا"
  },
  {
      "question": "همتارو",
      "response": "ه م ت ا ر و"
  },
  {
      "question": "الويفيا",
      "response": "ا ل و ي ف ي ا"
  },
  {
      "question": "نويل",
      "response": "ن و ي ل"
  },
  {
      "question": "رايلي",
      "response": "ر ا ي ل ي"
  },
  {
      "question": "ال",
      "response": "ا ل"
  },
  {
      "question": "لاو",
      "response": "ل ا و"
  },
  {
      "question": "مادارا",
      "response": "م ا د ا ر ا"
  },
  {
      "question": "يوريتشي",
      "response": "ي و ر ي ت ش ي"
  },
  {
      "question": "ايتاتشي",
      "response": "ا ي ت ا ت ش ي"
  },
  {
      "question": "توبي",
      "response": "ت و ب ي"
  },
  {
      "question": "نوبارا",
      "response": "ن و ب ا ر ا"
  },
  {
      "question": "ليفاي",
      "response": "ل ي ف ا ي"
  },
  {
      "question": "هاشيراما",
      "response": "ه ا ش ي ر ا م ا"
  },
  {
      "question": "بوروتو",
      "response": "ب و ر و ت و"
  },
  {
      "question": "يوسوب",
      "response": "ي و س و ب"
  },
  {
      "question": "ريم",
      "response": "ر ي م"
  },
  {
      "question": "اوتشيها شيسوي",
      "response": "ا و ت ش ي ه ا ش ي س و ي"
  },
  {
      "question": "كيد",
      "response": "ك ي د"
  },
  {
      "question": "ميكاسا",
      "response": "م ي ك ا س ا"
  },
  {
      "question": "دانزو",
      "response": "د ا ن ز و"
  },
  {
      "question": "وينغ",
      "response": "و ي ن غ"
  },
  {
      "question": "تينشيهان",
      "response": "ت ي ن ش ي ه ا ن"
  },
  {
      "question": "بيكوهان",
      "response": "ب ي ك و ه ا ن"
  },
  {
      "question": "كازيكاجي",
      "response": "ك ا ز ي ك ا ج ي"
  },
  {
      "question": "جيرايا",
      "response": "ج ي ر ا ي ا"
  },
  {
      "question": "كازيكاجي",
      "response": "ك ا ز ي ك ا ج ي"
  },
  {
      "question": "كوكومي",
      "response": "ك و ك و م ي"
  },
  {
      "question": "غيو",
      "response": "غ ي و"
  },
  {
      "question": "تشيو",
      "response": "ت ش ي و"
  },
  {
      "question": "ساسوري",
      "response": "س ا س و ر ي"
  },
  {
      "question": "نيزوكو",
      "response": "ن ي ز و ك و"
  },
  {
      "question": "ميدوريا",
      "response": "م ي د و ر ي ا"
  },
  {
      "question": "نيجي",
      "response": "ن ي ج ي"
  },
  {
      "question": "استا",
      "response": "ا س ت ا"
  },
  {
      "question": "ليزا",
      "response": "ل ي ز ا"
  },
  {
      "question": "كاغويا",
      "response": "ك ا غ و ي ا"
  },
  {
      "question": "هينا",
      "response": "ه ي ن ا"
  },
  {
      "question": "الوكا",
      "response": "ا ل و ك ا"
  },
  {
      "question": "هيناتا",
      "response": "ه ي ن ا ت ا"
  },
  {
      "question": "زينتسو",
      "response": "ز ي ن ت س و"
  },
  {
      "question": "رينغوكو",
      "response": "ر ي ن غ و ك و"
  },
  {
      "question": "ليفاي",
      "response": "ل ي ف ا ي"
  },
  {
      "question": "كورتا",
      "response": "ك و ر ت ا"
  },
  {
      "question": "هيسوكا",
      "response": "ه ي س و ك ا"
  },
  {
     "question": "انوس",
      "response": "ا ن و س"
  },
  {
     "question": "بياكوغان",
      "response": "ب ي ا ك و غ ا ن"
  },
  {
     "question": "شوكو",
      "response": "ش و ك و"
  },
  {
     "question": "ديكو",
      "response": "د ي ك و"
  },
  {
     "question": "يامي",
      "response": "ي ا م ي"
  },
  {
     "question": "فانجانس",
      "response": "ف ا ن ج ا ن س"
  },
  {
     "question": "يوليوس",
      "response": "ي و ل ي و س"
  },
  {
     "question": "تسوموغو",
      "response": "ت س و م و غ و"
  },
  {
     "question": "نانامي",
      "response": "ن ا ن ا م ي"
  },
  {
     "question": "ايزن",
      "response": "ا ي ز ن"
  },
  {
     "question": "زاراكي",
      "response": "ز ا ر ا ك ي"
  },
  {
     "question": "اوراهارا",
      "response": "ا و ر ا ه ا ر ا"
  },
  {
     "question": "اينوي",
      "response": "ا ي ن و ي"
  },
  {
     "question": "غوهان",
      "response": "غ و ه ا ن"
  },
  {
     "question": "كيريلين",
      "response": "ك ي ر ي ل ي ن"
  },
  {
     "question": "هيناتسورو",
      "response": "ه ي ن ا ت س و ر و"
  },
  {
     "question": "ر ي ت ش ي ل",
     "response": "ر ي ت ش ي ل"
}
]